export const QuizCamer=[
    {
        fournisseur:"Abdel Aziz",
        subject:"App to learn more about Cameroun",
        quizz: {
            beginner:[
                {
                    id: 0,
                    question:"When did Cameroon become independent?",
                    option:[
                        "1 January 1960",
                        "14 April 1956",
                        "17 July 1964",
                        "29 October 1972",
                    ],
                    answer: "1 January 1960",
                    camerId: 1001

                },
                {
                    id: 1,
                    question:" Who founded the city of Victoria in Cameroon and translated the Bible in Douala?",
                    option:[
                        "Alfred Saker",
                        "David Livingstone",
                        "Joseph Merrick",
                        "Robert Moffat",
                    ],
                    answer: "Alfred Saker",
                    camerId: 1002

                },
                {
                    id: 2,
                    question:"When did Fernao do Po sight Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "1492",
                        "1453",
                        "1472",
                        "1498",
                    ],
                    answer: "1472",
                    camerId: 1003
                },
                {
                    id: 3,
                    question:"When did Fernao do Po sight Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "1492",
                        "1453",
                        "1472",
                        "1498",
                    ],
                    answer: "1884",
                    camerId: 1004
                },
                {
                    id: 4,
                    question:"Which is the capital of Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "Garoua",
                        "Bamenda",
                        "Douala",
                        "Yaounde",
                    ],
                    answer: "Yaounde",
                    camerId: 1005
                },
                {
                    id: 5,
                    question:"Which is the currency of Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "Pound",
                        "Dollar",
                        "CFA Franc",
                        "Naira",
                    ],
                    answer: "CFA Franc",
                    camerId: 1006
                },
                {
                    id: 6,
                    question:"Who was Cameroon’s first president?",
                    option:[
                        "Ahmadou Ahidjo",
                        "Ephraim Inoni",
                        "Peter Mafani Musonge",
                        "Michel Moussala",
                    ],
                    answer: "Ahmadou Ahidjo",
                    camerId: 1007
                },
                {
                    id: 7,
                    question:"Which region was disputed between Cameroon and Nigeria?",
                    option:[
                        "Kano-Katsina",
                        "Bakassi Peninsula",
                        "Sokoto",
                        "Borno",
                    ],
                    answer: "Bakassi Peninsula",
                    camerId: 1008
                },
                {
                    id: 8,
                    question:"Who got elected as president of Cameroon in 1984 and 1988 elections being the only candidate?",
                    option:[
                        "Polycarpe Abah Abah",
                        "Simon Achidi Achu",
                        "Paul Biya",
                        "John Fru Ndi",
                    ],
                    answer: "Paul Biya",
                    camerId: 1009
                },
                {
                    id: 9,
                    question:"When did Cameroon first reach quarterfinals in Football World Cup?",
                    option:[
                        "1990",
                        "1974",
                        "1966",
                        "1978",
                    ],
                    answer: "1990",
                    camerId: 10010
                },
            ],
            intermediate:[
                {
                    id: 0,
                    question:"When did Cameroon become independent?",
                    option:[
                        "1 January 1960",
                        "14 April 1956",
                        "17 July 1964",
                        "29 October 1972",
                    ],
                    answer: "1 January 1960",
                    camerId: 1001

                },
                {
                    id: 1,
                    question:" Who founded the city of Victoria in Cameroon and translated the Bible in Douala?",
                    option:[
                        "Alfred Saker",
                        "David Livingstone",
                        "Joseph Merrick",
                        "Robert Moffat",
                    ],
                    answer: "Alfred Saker",
                    camerId: 1002

                },
                {
                    id: 2,
                    question:"When did Fernao do Po sight Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "1492",
                        "1453",
                        "1472",
                        "1498",
                    ],
                    answer: "1472",
                    camerId: 1003
                },
                {
                    id: 3,
                    question:"When did Fernao do Po sight Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "1492",
                        "1453",
                        "1472",
                        "1498",
                    ],
                    answer: "1884",
                    camerId: 1004
                },
                {
                    id: 4,
                    question:"Which is the capital of Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "Garoua",
                        "Bamenda",
                        "Douala",
                        "Yaounde",
                    ],
                    answer: "Yaounde",
                    camerId: 1005
                },
                {
                    id: 5,
                    question:"Which is the currency of Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "Pound",
                        "Dollar",
                        "CFA Franc",
                        "Naira",
                    ],
                    answer: "CFA Franc",
                    camerId: 1006
                },
                {
                    id: 6,
                    question:"Who was Cameroon’s first president?",
                    option:[
                        "Ahmadou Ahidjo",
                        "Ephraim Inoni",
                        "Peter Mafani Musonge",
                        "Michel Moussala",
                    ],
                    answer: "Ahmadou Ahidjo",
                    camerId: 1007
                },
                {
                    id: 7,
                    question:"Which region was disputed between Cameroon and Nigeria?",
                    option:[
                        "Kano-Katsina",
                        "Bakassi Peninsula",
                        "Sokoto",
                        "Borno",
                    ],
                    answer: "Bakassi Peninsula",
                    camerId: 1008
                },
                {
                    id: 8,
                    question:"Who got elected as president of Cameroon in 1984 and 1988 elections being the only candidate?",
                    option:[
                        "Polycarpe Abah Abah",
                        "Simon Achidi Achu",
                        "Paul Biya",
                        "John Fru Ndi",
                    ],
                    answer: "Paul Biya",
                    camerId: 1009
                },
                {
                    id: 9,
                    question:"When did Cameroon first reach quarterfinals in Football World Cup?",
                    option:[
                        "1990",
                        "1974",
                        "1966",
                        "1978",
                    ],
                    answer: "1990",
                    camerId: 10010
                },
            ],
            expert:[
                {
                    id: 0,
                    question:"When did Cameroon become independent?",
                    option:[
                        "1 January 1960",
                        "14 April 1956",
                        "17 July 1964",
                        "29 October 1972",
                    ],
                    answer: "1 January 1960",
                    camerId: 1001

                },
                {
                    id: 1,
                    question:" Who founded the city of Victoria in Cameroon and translated the Bible in Douala?",
                    option:[
                        "Alfred Saker",
                        "David Livingstone",
                        "Joseph Merrick",
                        "Robert Moffat",
                    ],
                    answer: "Alfred Saker",
                    camerId: 1002

                },
                {
                    id: 2,
                    question:"When did Fernao do Po sight Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "1492",
                        "1453",
                        "1472",
                        "1498",
                    ],
                    answer: "1472",
                    camerId: 1003
                },
                {
                    id: 3,
                    question:"When did Fernao do Po sight Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "1492",
                        "1453",
                        "1472",
                        "1498",
                    ],
                    answer: "1884",
                    camerId: 1004
                },
                {
                    id: 4,
                    question:"Which is the capital of Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "Garoua",
                        "Bamenda",
                        "Douala",
                        "Yaounde",
                    ],
                    answer: "Yaounde",
                    camerId: 1005
                },
                {
                    id: 5,
                    question:"Which is the currency of Cameroon?",
                    option:[
                        "Pound",
                        "Dollar",
                        "CFA Franc",
                        "Naira",
                    ],
                    answer: "CFA Franc",
                    camerId: 1006
                },
                {
                    id: 6,
                    question:"Who was Cameroon’s first president?",
                    option:[
                        "Ahmadou Ahidjo",
                        "Ephraim Inoni",
                        "Peter Mafani Musonge",
                        "Michel Moussala",
                    ],
                    answer: "Ahmadou Ahidjo",
                    camerId: 1007
                },
                {
                    id: 7,
                    question:"Which region was disputed between Cameroon and Nigeria?",
                    option:[
                        "Kano-Katsina",
                        "Bakassi Peninsula",
                        "Sokoto",
                        "Borno",
                    ],
                    answer: "Bakassi Peninsula",
                    camerId: 1008
                },
                {
                    id: 8,
                    question:"Who got elected as president of Cameroon in 1984 and 1988 elections being the only candidate?",
                    option:[
                        "Polycarpe Abah Abah",
                        "Simon Achidi Achu",
                        "Paul Biya",
                        "John Fru Ndi",
                    ],
                    answer: "Paul Biya",
                    camerId: 1009
                },
                {
                    id: 9,
                    question:"When did Cameroon first reach quarterfinals in Football World Cup?",
                    option:[
                        "1990",
                        "1974",
                        "1966",
                        "1978",
                    ],
                    answer: "1990",
                    camerId: 10010
                },
            ]
        }
    }
]